Shuhang Xu

Pleasant Hill, California, United States



xushuhang0805@gmail.com



7075902145



linkedin.com/in/shuhang-xu-1805821a5

Summary

Associate degree in Diablo Valley College, CS, 4.0 Pursuing Bachelor of Science in UCSD, CS, 4.0 Interned in Yektasonics inc., Ambitious Analytics Lab Five awards in California PBL Business Competition Served in multiple clubs in DVC and UCSD as club leaders

Experience



CSE Tutor

UC San Diego Computer Science and Engineering Department (CSE)

Mar 2022 - Present (5 months +)

Spring 2022: CSE 15L(Software Tools and Techniques)

Summer 2022: CSE 140(Components and Design Techniques for Digital Systems)

Vice President

Chinese Computer Community at UCSD

Oct 2021 - Present (10 months +)

President

DVC Chinese Student Association

Sep 2020 - Jun 2021 (10 months)

Chinese Student Association is a student-run organization aiding international students in academics and career planning.

As the President, I

- Organized regular activities for 120+ members to help them better assimilate into college.
- Led BCC, CCSF, CSM, and 8 other colleges to organize 6 transfer workshops and social networking events.

Commissioner of Tech & Outreach Operation, Inter-Club Council

Associated Students of Diablo Valley College

Sep 2020 - May 2021 (9 months)

- Worked with 5 ASDVC Technical officers:
- Promoted 10+ ICC events on social media.
- Prepared devices and projector for weekly collaborative meetings between 2 campuses.
- Updated and emailed newsletters to 200+ reps.

DVC President

TasselLink

Apr 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 2 months)

- Collaborated with 50+ non-profits and 30+ companies to provide internship and volunteer opportunities for members.
- Organized transfer workshops attended by 250.
- Collated 200+ academic resources for 56 club members

Share Vice President of External Affairs

iShare

Jan 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 5 months)

- Planned 6 career development workshops for 160 members.
- Invited 2 UCB alum working in Goldman Sachs as speakers.
- Managed social media promotions.
- Led to 600+ website views, 80+ new newsletter subscriptions.

Software Engineer Intern

YektaSonics Inc.

Jul 2020 - Aug 2020 (2 months)

- Refined the brain image analysis and data files organization to enhance the software accuracy.
- Assisted in developing a non-invasive treatments through an ultrasonic stimulator for various clinical conditions.
- Provided ad-hoc supports and version control on the software for the development team.

Software Engineer Intern

Ambitious Analytics Lab

Jun 2020 - Jul 2020 (2 months)

- Assisted the company in developing 2 data analysis programs using Programming Languages R and
- Integrated Shiny into WordPress to enable publications of Apps on the website.
- Recommended that the team offer 3 free trials to users, increasing the number of user feedbacks by more than 25%.

Education



UC San Diego

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

Sep 2021 - May 2023 Current GPA: 4.0



UC San Diego Jacobs School of Engineering

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

Sep 2021 - May 2023

Current GPA: 4.0

DVC Diablo Valley College

Associate of Science - AS, Computer Science

Licenses & Certifications



- **1st Place, California PBL Entrepreneurship Competition** California Phi Beta Lambda, Inc.
- 1st place, California PBL Business Presentation Case Comp. California Phi Beta Lambda, Inc.
- **2nd Place, California PBL Impromptu Speaking Competition** California Phi Beta Lambda, Inc.
- 5th place, California PBL Networking (CS) Competition California Phi Beta Lambda, Inc.

Skills

Software • Hardware • MATLAB • R (Programming Language) • C++ • Java • Git • Android Studio • Product Management